{
    "subject": "resource/Cycling_at_the_1924_Summer_Olympics_\u2013_Men's_team_pursuit",
    "predicate": "ontology/silverMedalist",
    "object": "resource/Franciszek_Szymczyk",
    "human_readable": "Franciszek Szymczyk was the silver medalist in the men's team pursuit at the 1924 Summer Olympics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9146525859832764,
            "question": "In which year did Franciszek Szymczyk win a medal at the Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.909681499004364,
            "question": "At which Olympic Games did Franciszek Szymczyk win a medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.889510989189148,
            "question": "Who was Franciszek Szymczyk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8607364296913147,
            "question": "What type of medal did Franciszek Szymczyk win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8525173664093018,
            "question": "What event did Franciszek Szymczyk compete in at the Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7434975504875183,
            "question": "What sport did Franciszek Szymczyk compete in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7199258208274841,
            "question": "Was Franciszek Szymczyk competing individually or as part of a team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5096033215522766,
            "question": "What does it mean to be a silver medalist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21166296303272247,
            "question": "What is the significance of winning an Olympic medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.030507635325193405,
            "question": "Do you know any other notable athletes from Poland?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Franciszek Szymczyk was the silver medalist in the men's team pursuit at the 1924 Summer Olympics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6291_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of winning an Olympic medal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6291_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does it mean to be a silver medalist?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6291_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Franciszek Szymczyk competing individually or as part of a team?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6291_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6291_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6291_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6291_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6291_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6291_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6291_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6291_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6291_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6291_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6291_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Franciszek Ksawery Szymczyk won a silver medal as part of the Polish track cycling team in the team pursuit event during the 1924 Summer Olympics. This information directly supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}